liebertpub.com 2012-12-30

# Privacy Policy Title

## Mary Ann Liebert Inc. & Liebertpub.com Privacy Policy

Mary Ann Liebert, Inc. (Liebert) and liebertpub.com (the "Site") are committed to protecting your privacy. As a user of the Site, you acknowledge that we will collect certain information about you, and that you may provide information regarding your interests and preferences. This statement sets forth our Privacy Policy and describes the practices liebertpub.com follows with respect to information provided by visitors to this Site. Please be aware that this Site may contain links to other sites that are covered by their own privacy policies.

#### How We Use Your Personal Information

**Newsletter and Email Communications Subscribers** **:  
**When you fill out our Opt-In form, we use the contact information you provide to send you journal alerts, complimentary articles, news updates, and special offers on the journals you requested or other related Liebert journals.

**Website Users:  
**To purchase items via our Site and/or to request information, you must provide some basic information such as: name, email and contact information. We use this information for internal purposes only namely, processing your orders, notifying you of your order status, updating your account, sending you notices of new services, and noteworthy news and events.

  **We do not sell or rent information about our customers or email lists to third parties.**

** ** If you would like to change your registration or opt-out of receiving email from us, you can send an email to [connect@liebertpub.com](mailto:connect@liebertpub.com) and type “Unsubscribe from ‘Journal Name’” in the subject line to remove yourself from a particular journal list or “Unsubscribe from all” to remove yourself from all email communication. We will process your request within 10 days. You can also manage your account by clicking on the links at the bottom of your email.

Any personal data you may provide is used to create personalized content and services on our Site, as well as to better understand the interests and preferences of our members and customers. 

**Change of Address or Contact Information  
**If your email address or contact information has changed or is incorrect, please update your user account information or send an email to [info@liebertpub.com](mailto:info@liebertpub.com).

**Cookies  
**When you visit our Site, liebertpub.com may send your computer a "cookie," a small file that resides on your computer's hard drive and stores information about your website preferences. Our cookies do not store any personal identifying information and none of our cookies ever live beyond the end of a single user's session. We may collect certain information about all users of the Site such as an Internet Protocol (IP) address, the type of browser and operating system used, the date and time visited, and the pages visited. This information is captured for our usage in learning about our visitors, to help us continually improve your online experience with our firm. Please note that blocking cookies may prevent you from accessing all of the features of the Site.

If you have questions about liebertpub.com's Privacy Policy or concerns about personal information you have supplied to liebertpub.com, please send an email to [info@liebertpub.com](mailto:info@liebertpub.com).
